Stephan van Deventer

Full-Stack Developer hi@polarizedions.net Robertson, ZA



I know a lot

React C# Javascript VueJS MySQL Postgres
Docker NodeJS Java Linux Git Typescript
HTML5 CSS3 Traefik EFCore Scrum
TailwindCSS JWT Nginx Jira Jenkins GCP AWS
Visual Studio Visual Studio Code Rider Slack



polarisa.dev



polarisa.dev/linkedin



polarisa.dev/cv



polarizedions.net

About Me

I am a friendly, passionate, full stack developer from South Africa. Although my years in the workforce aren't that long, I have a lot of experience in many web-based technologies. I am always learning something new, working on one project or another. I am a fast learner, with great logic skills, and have a keen eye for design elements.

Experience

WEBelieveIT — Fullstack Web Developer MARCH 2019 - PRESENT

- Contract work for The Delta Studios (thedelta.io), working on Priv (priv-io.com)
 - Building with React to build a Digital Privacy Management tool, using C#, ReactJS, and Postgres
- Contract work for SQN (sqn.world), building front- and backend apps/systems
 - 3G platform stack: KnockoutJS, SemanticUI, VueJS, Javascript, Nginx, Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins, C#, Java, Python, jQuery, MySQL, git
 - 5G platform stack: VueJS, Bootstrap, Typescript, NodeJS, Codefresh,
 Docker, Kubernetes (with helm charts), MySQL, git (bitbucket)
- Work on TimeTracker (timetracker.co.za), both front- and backend
 - Stack: C# (dotnet core), Dapper, Javascript, VueJS, SemanticUI, Jenkins
 (Declarative Pipeline), Docker, bash scripts, MySQL, git (bitbucket)
 - DevOps role to manage our internal infrastructure
 - Jenkins, Docker, NetData, Portainer, Traefik, Sonarqube Nexus, PiHole, Nginx, Linux (Debian)

Breededesign — Intern JANUARY 2019 - APRIL 2019

- Internship, working on designing and building client websites.
 - Using WordPress & Divi Theme, FTP, CSS, Photoshop

Education

Robertson High School — Matric / NSC 2012 - 2016

- Passed IT in matric with 87% (classes at Worcester Gymnasium)
- Did well in other classes like Physical Sciences, Biology, English, and Math
- 73% Average in Matric
- Go-to backstage-helper & -coordinator for events, functions, and the School Revue

Awards

- Runner-up for the South African Programing Olympiad 2016 (placed in the top 20 out of all participants in the country)
- Prize for top IT result in highschool for matric (87%)